// CODE QUIZ: 10 true and false questions and their answers
var questions = [
    {
        question: 'The closest() method searches for a match within parent relationships whereas the querySelector() method searches for a match within descendent relationships.',
        options: ['T', 'F'], 
        answer: 'T',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: the statement above is true."
    },
    {
        question: 'DOM stands for Document Object Model', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'T',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: the statement above is true."
    },
    {
        question: 'API stands for Application Parameter Interface', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'F',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: API stands for Application Programming Interface"
    },
    {
        question: 'answer callback function is passed as an argument to another function', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'T',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: the statement above is true."
    },
    {
        question: 'JavaScript data types include numbers, strings, objects, boolean, function, and array', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'T',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: the statement above is true."
    },
    {
        question: 'Parameters are the actual value/s that get/s passed through the parameter into the function to be used', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'F',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: Parameters are placeholder variables where their values are defined when the function is called and are not assigned values within the function itself'"
    },
    {
        question: 'Arguments are placeholder variables where their values are defined when the function is called and are not assigned values within the function itself', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'F',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: Arguments are are the actual value/s that get/s passed through the parameter into the function to be used."
    },
    {
        question: 'JSON stands for JavaScript Object Notification', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'F',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: JSON stands for Javascript Object Notation"
    },
    {
        question: 'Two browser specific functions that can be used to gather user input are <prompt> and <confirm>', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'T',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: the statement above is true."
    },
    {
        question: 'It is a best practice to assign reserved words as variables.', 
        options: ['T', 'F'],
        answer: 'F',
        ifWrong: "INCORRECT: reserved words like 'default' and 'export' should not be used as variables."
    },
]